{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702496878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702496877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 5a5134c5-d423-44eb-ab11-4f397a368df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702522608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702522607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 5a5134c5-d423-44eb-ab11-4f397a368df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702526335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702526334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 5a5134c5-d423-44eb-ab11-4f397a368df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702526812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702526811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 5a5134c5-d423-44eb-ab11-4f397a368df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702536792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702536791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 5a5134c5-d423-44eb-ab11-4f397a368df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702550931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702550931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" f0c5c0bf-e777-4252-9c37-15148c9e7993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702554515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702554514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" f0c5c0bf-e777-4252-9c37-15148c9e7993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702556185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702556184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" f0c5c0bf-e777-4252-9c37-15148c9e7993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702559955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702559954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" f0c5c0bf-e777-4252-9c37-15148c9e7993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702562012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702562011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" f0c5c0bf-e777-4252-9c37-15148c9e7993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702562372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702562371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" f0c5c0bf-e777-4252-9c37-15148c9e7993"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702576318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702576318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702579781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702579780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702581426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702581425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702585243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702585242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702587317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702587316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702587782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702587781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702594101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702594100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 9591f80c-9774-43db-b3ed-0eaa7bfa3eea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702607593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702607593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702611104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702611103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yangu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702612738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702612737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702616679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702616679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702618735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702618734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702619108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702619108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702628510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702628509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.122","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702636503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702636501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" a756f9b6-9307-4ced-ab42-dd248d55b7ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Y.rand.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702643838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702643837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 6ab82f87-c575-4ce6-a942-bab156fa5bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702676839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702676839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 6ab82f87-c575-4ce6-a942-bab156fa5bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702679571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702679569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 6ab82f87-c575-4ce6-a942-bab156fa5bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702679974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702679974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220758"," gameId":" 6ab82f87-c575-4ce6-a942-bab156fa5bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"end":"end"}]}